<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Calling Card</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_heroku">Heroku</string>

    <string name="heroku">Heroku</string>
    <string name="close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="reverse">REVERSE</string>
    <string name="source">SOURCE</string>
    <string name="empty_error">Enter some text</string>

    <string name="heroku_text">
        Enter some text above then click the button to send the text to a node.js application running on Heroku to reverse it.
        There may be a delay while the Heroku instance starts up.
        Click below to see the source code on Github.
    </string>

    <string name="home_introduction">
        Hello, have a look through my profile below, and slide from the left to see the other sections of this app.
        Please click the icons above to contact me, or to view the source code for this app.
    </string>
    <string name="primary_skills">
        Android design and development
        \nWeb services and REST APIs
        \nApp hosting (Heroku, Amazon Web Services)
        \nUnit testing
        \nTest driven development and Agile
        \nContinuous integration and automatic testing
        \nTechnical team leadership
    </string>
    <string name="primary_languages">
        Java (Android, desktop, JNI)
        \nKotlin (Android)
        \nC/C++
        \nJavaScript (node.js, Express, socket.io)
        \nAssembler (x86, ARM)
    </string>
    <string name="primary_libraries">
        Reactive (Rx)
        \nDagger 2
        \nRetrofit/OkHttp
        \nButterknife
        \nGlide/Picasso
        \nMockito
    </string>
    <string name="primary_dyson">
        Part of a close team of Android, iOS and cloud developers, testers, UI designers and scrum facilitators, adding new features to the Dyson Link app to support new products.
        The app uses MVVM architecture, and multiple modules and flavours. The development cycle is supported by the Atlassian suite (Jira, Bamboo, Stash, Hipchat).
    </string>
    <string name="primary_xing">
        Working within a large distributed team, responsible for the re-development of a major section of the client’s app using MVP architecture.
        Also porting existing Cucumber (Calabash) tests from the iOS app to Android. Extensive use of the back-end cloud API using background tasks.
        Thorough unit test coverage of the logic (presenter) layer using Mockito.
    </string>
    <string name="primary_radiodetection">
        The client manufactures specialist hardware with both Bluetooth Classic and Bluetooth Low Energy capabilities and needed an Android app to communicate with it.
        The app was also required to interface to a web REST service and a local Realm ORM database. There was an existing app but it needed overhauling to increase reliability and add features.
        Designed and developed a new architecture using modern Android development practices including Rx, Dagger, Retrofit, OkHttp, Material Design and automated stress testing,
        together with direct use of Android APIs for Bluetooth connectivity.
    </string>
    <string name="primary_abaco">
        The client needed a low-level driver and access API to support custom hardware.
        Addressed issues with existing build system then designed and wrote a Windows hardware driver using C/C++.
        Designed and wrote an access API to the end-user’s requirements, again in C/C++.
        Many technical challenges were involved, e.g. working on custom hardware without usual PC connectivity, cross-platform debugging, low-level hardware interaction.
    </string>
    <string name="primary_mubaloo">
        Developed Android applications to customer specifications, working within a small team of other Android developers, iOS developers and UX/UI designers.
        Worked within tight timescales, using digital assets supplied by the design team, ensuring that the app had a consistent look-and-feel across platforms.
        Apps used MVP, Reactive and dependency injection, and interacted with several web services using Retrofit/OkHttp.
    </string>
    <string name="primary_babcock">
        Led the development of a tablet-based Android app to enable efficient data collection.
        Restrictions on the target environment meant the need for inventive solutions to data transfer - implemented
        low-level socket proxies over USB to allow use of mobile database synchronisation (Couchbase).
        Implemented web front and back ends for dynamic UI on the device (Java REST and Server Faces).
    </string>
    <string name="primary_zebra">
        I worked with the other architects on the design of a new mobile enterprise app development toolkit,
        then ran a team of Windows Mobile/CE and Android developers in its implementation.
        The project required in-depth Android knowledge, including GUI, logic, architecture and JNI/NDK,
        targeting both enterprise and consumer Android devices.
        \nI oversaw the collaboration of the UK team with teams in other countries to integrate Motorola’s own product with the Rhodes product to create the RhoMobileSuite cross platform development framework.
        \nI led the design and implementation of a CI/ATS framework, running on Amazon EC-2 instances. It uses REST APIs, implemented in node.js, to enable globally distributed mobile devices to execute test suites.
        By using the Github and S3 APIs it performs cloud-based test builds.
    </string>
    <string name="primary_interaxis">
        These were my own companies where I employed a small team developing custom solutions in the data collection and mobile data processing industry.
        I ran all aspects of the business: I understood customers’ requirements, I won the contract, I designed the solution and organised the team to deliver it.
        \nDevelopment was principally in C# .NET, but also used cross-compiled C for embedded systems.
    </string>
    <string name="primary_education">
        I left school in 1985 with 5 A-levels (Maths, Further Maths, Physics, Chemistry, General Studies) and went on to study Maths at King\'s College, London.
    </string>

</resources>
